<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>TDD on Crying Bear Studio</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/tags/tdd/</link><description>Recent content in TDD on Crying Bear Studio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 19:26:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.cryingbear.net/tags/tdd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Unit Testing Dilemma</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-09-10-a-unit-testing-dilemma/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 19:26:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-09-10-a-unit-testing-dilemma/</guid><description>After returning to blogging after a really long hiatus with some really heavy and emotional stuff, I think I&amp;rsquo;m way the hell overdue for a development-related post.
I&amp;rsquo;ve long been a believer that one of the most important and most overlooked aspects of TDD is making sure the test fails first. To put it another way, here&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Gandalf&amp;rsquo;s First Law of Unit Testing&amp;rdquo;:
You shall not pass!
— Gandalf the Grey, in his first (and last) TDD seminar</description></item><item><title>Methodologists</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-02-20-methodologists/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 20:40:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-02-20-methodologists/</guid><description>Once upon a time, way back before I was even married, much less a divorced dad, my brother Andy and I worked together at a certain company. This was my first professional job and the beginning of my long, sordid IT career and I owe it all to nepotism.
Anyway, shortly after I started at this company, there was an internal change in management and our divisional president was replaced with a new hire - a fellow of South Asian extraction.</description></item><item><title>The most important effect of practicing TDD</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-01-27-the-most-important-effect-of-practicing-tdd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-01-27-the-most-important-effect-of-practicing-tdd/</guid><description>For the last couple weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been helping to interview candidates for a vacancy on my company&amp;rsquo;s development team. Experience with TDD is not a prerequisite for our candidates (although openness to it certainly is), but occasionally we&amp;rsquo;ll get an applicant who claims to have some previous TDD experience at a previous position. One of the questions I always pose to a candidate in this category is &amp;ldquo;what would you say is the most important effect of practicing TDD?</description></item></channel></rss>