<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Fossils on Crying Bear Studio</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/</link><description>Recent content in Fossils on Crying Bear Studio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Maven: I still just don't get it.</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2011-01-11-maven-i-still-just-dont-get-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 22:08:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2011-01-11-maven-i-still-just-dont-get-it/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m in the process of trying to kick off another hobby coding project, this time in the Android ecosystem (toxic as that seems to be - more on that in another post someday)1. Remembering how a few current and former colleagues have raved about Maven, especially how one particular former colleague told me I needed to &amp;ldquo;suck it up and learn Maven&amp;rdquo;, I decided to give it another shot.
Grabbing a very small and straightforward sample pom.</description></item><item><title>Find the hidden Microsoft message...</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2010-09-11-find-the-hidden-microsoft-message/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2010 15:03:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2010-09-11-find-the-hidden-microsoft-message/</guid><description>After rebuilding my Windows 7 VM from scratch, I (of course) installed the latest Visual Studio 2010. The first time I ran it, it prompted me to choose my default settings. This is nothing new - Visual Studio has had this dialog for as many versions as I remember. The difference is, this time I actually noticed the &amp;ldquo;flavor text&amp;rdquo; that they include to describe the different configurations - I&amp;rsquo;d never previously paid any attention to it.</description></item><item><title>Не знает счастья только тот, Кто его зова понять не смог...</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2010-08-04-ne-znaet-schastia-tolko-tot-kto-ego-zova-poniat-ne-smog/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2010 01:40:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2010-08-04-ne-znaet-schastia-tolko-tot-kto-ego-zova-poniat-ne-smog/</guid><description>Origa is the single biggest reason I want to learn Russian&amp;hellip;
Пока жива, я могу стараться на лету не упасть,
Не разучиться мечтать&amp;hellip;любить&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;Бесконечный бег&amp;hellip; 1
Calling Calling, For the place of knowing
There&amp;rsquo;s more that what can be linked
Calling Calling, Never will I look away
For what life has left for me
Yearning Yearning, for what&amp;rsquo;s left of loving
Собой остаться дольше&amp;hellip; 2
— Inner Universe by Origa and Shanti Snyder</description></item><item><title>Living Lean?</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2010-03-22-living-lean/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 19:57:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2010-03-22-living-lean/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m feeling pretty silly that this idea has never occurred to me before now. Being into all the bleeding-edge Agile software stuff as I am, I&amp;rsquo;ve been familiar with the basics of Lean Manufacturing for a few years now. But for some reason, it never crossed my mind until tonight to try to apply Lean concepts to my everyday life outside a workplace setting.
The specific part of life I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about is losing weight.</description></item><item><title>Speed up your builds by 9.5% instantly!</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-10-27-speed-up-your-builds-by-9-5-instantly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2009 12:23:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-10-27-speed-up-your-builds-by-9-5-instantly/</guid><description>Nope, despite the tone of the title, I&amp;rsquo;m not selling a product, even though it does sound like a sales pitch. But I did just do this on the builds on my team, and I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share. And though it&amp;rsquo;s really not a revolutionary process, I&amp;rsquo;ve removed a guaranteed 1 minute and 6 seconds from every build cycle by deleting one line of code in one production class, and refactoring a constant into an injectable property in another.</description></item><item><title>A Unit Testing Dilemma</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-09-10-a-unit-testing-dilemma/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 19:26:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-09-10-a-unit-testing-dilemma/</guid><description>After returning to blogging after a really long hiatus with some really heavy and emotional stuff, I think I&amp;rsquo;m way the hell overdue for a development-related post.
I&amp;rsquo;ve long been a believer that one of the most important and most overlooked aspects of TDD is making sure the test fails first. To put it another way, here&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Gandalf&amp;rsquo;s First Law of Unit Testing&amp;rdquo;:
You shall not pass!
— Gandalf the Grey, in his first (and last) TDD seminar</description></item><item><title>A Long Overdue Reality Check (@wundarous)</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-08-15-a-long-overdue-reality-check-wundarous/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2009 23:17:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-08-15-a-long-overdue-reality-check-wundarous/</guid><description>For the last month or so, I&amp;rsquo;ve been in a largely dark and unhappy mood. There&amp;rsquo;s been a confluence of events and factors which have led to this depressive fugue, including (but not limited to):
Self-image; I now weigh more than I ever have in my life, and am precariously close to a big, round, psychologically-significant number of pounds Money; my credit score is at a precariously low point for someone employed by a credit-card processor, and the interest rate on a huge and maxed-out unsecured line-of-credit was recently hiked to usurious levels Living arrangements; I recently went through a stressful apartment move, though I honestly can&amp;rsquo;t point my finger at the stress points Loneliness; being recently divorced, I had physical custody of my daughter for most of the summer.</description></item><item><title>Methodologists</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-02-20-methodologists/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2009 20:40:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-02-20-methodologists/</guid><description>Once upon a time, way back before I was even married, much less a divorced dad, my brother Andy and I worked together at a certain company. This was my first professional job and the beginning of my long, sordid IT career and I owe it all to nepotism.
Anyway, shortly after I started at this company, there was an internal change in management and our divisional president was replaced with a new hire - a fellow of South Asian extraction.</description></item><item><title>STL Agile Beer Night, Iteration 1 - Retrospective</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-02-19-stl-agile-beer-night-iteration-1-retrospective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2009 21:11:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-02-19-stl-agile-beer-night-iteration-1-retrospective/</guid><description>Tonight we had STL Agile Beer Night, Iteration 1. It was lightly attended; I can see I&amp;rsquo;m going to have to work on the finer points of scheduling for a diverse audience. I think that next time I&amp;rsquo;ll get some sort of a poll going beforehand with a selection of different dates to see what draws the most potential attendance.
Tonight&amp;rsquo;s beer night consisted of myself, Brian Button, Zac Duncan and Jim Durtschy.</description></item><item><title>Lost Generation by Jonathan Reed</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-01-28-lost-generation-by-jonathan-reed/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2009 11:53:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-01-28-lost-generation-by-jonathan-reed/</guid><description>This is just too cool to not share:
Via Jason Yip,
Via Next Level - Digital Culture,
A reading of the poem Lost Generation by Jonathan Reed,</description></item><item><title>The most important effect of practicing TDD</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-01-27-the-most-important-effect-of-practicing-tdd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 23:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-01-27-the-most-important-effect-of-practicing-tdd/</guid><description>For the last couple weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been helping to interview candidates for a vacancy on my company&amp;rsquo;s development team. Experience with TDD is not a prerequisite for our candidates (although openness to it certainly is), but occasionally we&amp;rsquo;ll get an applicant who claims to have some previous TDD experience at a previous position. One of the questions I always pose to a candidate in this category is &amp;ldquo;what would you say is the most important effect of practicing TDD?</description></item><item><title>Personal Finance FAIL</title><link>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-01-27-personal-finance-fail/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2009 15:11:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>http://www.cryingbear.net/fossils/2009-01-27-personal-finance-fail/</guid><description>Ain&amp;rsquo;t it the truth, though? *sigh*</description></item></channel></rss>